luxurysociety.com 2014-06-25

# Luxury Society - Privacy Policy

This Website is edited by Digital Luxury Group, DLG SA, a Swiss Company incorporated under n° CHE-101.525.197 in Geneva and hosted by WOPATA, 73, rue Leyteire, 33000 Bordeaux FRANCE.

As LUXURY SOCIETY is a community that is all about trust we feel it is important to share our privacy policy with you. If you have any questions about this policy we can be reached by email at [privacy@luxurysociety.com](mailto:privacy@luxurysociety.com) or alternatively you can contact us at: LUXURY SOCIETY - Privacy Policy, Digital Luxury Group, DLG SA at 7 avenue Krieg, 1208 Geneva, Switzerland.

The Luxury Society Site contains links to other Web sites over which we have no control. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites to which you choose to link from our Sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other Web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.

**Collection and Use of Information by Luxury Society**

When you register with LUXURY SOCIETY and create your Member account you agree to provide us with some personal information such as your name, your professional and personal email addresses, country, location, occupation, password and any other personal or preference information that you voluntarily provide us with.

When you enter LUXURY SOCIETY website we collect website use information as you interact with LUXURY SOCIETY website such as your browser type and IP address. This information is automatically gathered for all visitors of Luxury Society website.

If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a contact about our site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your contact's email address. LUXURY SOCIETY stores the email addresses that Members provide so that we automatically send your contact an email or instant message and up to three reminders inviting him or her to visit the site. Recipients of invitations from LUXURY SOCIETY may contact LUXURY SOCIETY to request the removal of their information from our database.

Members may also store email addresses of people they know in their internal LUXURY SOCIETY address book and may also choose to send invitations and other communications to those addresses. You may prevent LUXURY SOCIETY email invitations and other messages from being sent to any email address you control by sending a single email with the subject "BLOCK" to [privacy@luxurysociety.com](mailto:privacy@luxurysociety.com) Please note that the email must come from the account you wish to block.

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

We offer a Public Profile feature which allows Members to publish portions of their Member profile, (including their name, current position, company, city, country, industry) to the public Internet. Members may choose the information available through that feature (CV, picture …) or opt-out of this feature by editing their account and settings.

However, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that Public Profile information will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of your Public Profile may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if third parties have copied or stored your Public Profile information.

**Our Use of Your Information**

We use the information we gather on Luxury Society to customize your experience and the advertisements you see, to store your preferences and record session information. The information we collect is used for internal review to improve the content of our Website, to conduct research and analysis to help improve your experience, to ensure the technical functionality of our network, and to create and develop new ideas and services for our Members.

Luxury Society may use your email to communicate with you and notify you of new services, professional happenings such as events and other special offers from our partners. Luxury Society may also send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the Luxury Society Services.

In addition, you may receive free informational newsletters from us relating to topics that may be of special interest to you.   
Members who no longer wish to receive updates, notifications or newsletters may choose not to by selecting 'Do not send me notification emails' in the Member profile 'Privacy Settings'. All notification emails and LUXURY SOCIETY newsletters also include the above instructions for opting-out of those communications in the future.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by emailing us [privacy@luxurysociety.com](mailto:privacy@luxurysociety.com)

Please provide us with your exact name and address if you write to us. We will be sure your name is removed.

**Choices Regarding the Disclosure of Personal Information to Others**

Except in connection with the foregoing uses of your personal information, we will not sell, rent, loan or give away your personally identifiable information to third parties without your prior written permission, unless required to do so by law or where we believe such action is necessary in order to protect or defend us or other third parties against error, negligence, breach of contract, theft, fraud and other illegal or harmful activity, to comply with our audit and security requirements, and to audit compliance with or corporate policies, procedures, legal and contractual obligations.

We also disclose and transfer information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of our business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event we become the subject of a bankruptcy proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, we or our trustee in bankruptcy may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court. You will be notified of sale of all or a substantial portion of our business to a third party via email or through a prominent notice posted on the Sites.

From time to time, we may use personal information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. In such event, we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

If you have a Luxury Society Member profile, other Members of Luxury Society may access your profile, however, they will not have access to your contact information and your contact information is not displayed in any Luxury Society profile.

**Posting to Public Areas of Luxury Society**

You post Content (as defined in the Luxury Society's Terms and Conditions) on the Site at your own risk. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.   
We have implemented commercially reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes.

We cannot control the actions of other Members with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your Content.

**Use of Cookies**

Like most websites, Luxury Society uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows Luxury Society to recognize you as a Member when you return to the Luxury Society website using the same computer and web browser. If your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use the Luxury Society website. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on our website.

One type of cookie, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you have logged in to your Luxury Society account. The next time you visit the Luxury Society website, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing Member so you will not need to log in before using the Service.

Additionally, if you log out of the Luxury Society website you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a “session” cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the Luxury Society website. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.

We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing Member preferences and tracking Member trends. In the course of serving advertisements or optimizing services to our Member, we may allow authorized third parties to place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Any information provided to third parties through such cookies will not be personally identifiable but may provide general segment information, e.g. your industry or geographic location, your occupation, or information about your professional or educational background, for greater customization of your Member experience. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies or you opt to refuse all cookies, you may not be able to use the Luxury Society website or services. Luxury Society does not store personally identifiable information in the cookies.

**Log files**

Each time you access a page or a file from the Luxury Society website, Luxury Society will save the following data in a Log file:   
\- Your IP address (by which your computer can be clearly identified),   
\- The name and IP address of the computer requesting the respective page from the Luxury Society website,   
\- The time, status, and amount of the transferred data, as well as the Internet website from which you have reached the requested page of the Luxury Society website   
\- The product and release information from your Internet browser.

This Log file will be stored securely on the website using industry best practice methods for safeguarding information and server functions.

IP addresses and hostnames are not linked to any individual's personally identifiable information and specific IP addresses and hostnames will not be made publicly available They will only be used by website log file software to compile overall summary statistical reports on the performance of the website.

Luxury Society uses the data from this Log file in anonymous form without reference to any member account for statistical purposes. In doing so, Luxury Society may analyze on which days and at which time the Luxury Society Services are particularly frequented and how much data volume is created on the Luxury Society website. Furthermore, by using the Log file, Luxury Society can identify defects on the Luxury Society Services, such as defective hyperlinks or program defects, and thus continually improve the quality of the Luxury Society Services. Luxury Society does not attribute the website demands stored in the Log file to specific individual users.

However, Luxury Society reserves the right to review the Log files from the last known IP address of a Luxury Society Member where Luxury Society has reasonable cause to believe that the Member is using the Luxury Society Services in breach of contractual agreements or the applicable legislation. In doing this, Luxury Society is protecting other Luxury Society Members, the safety of Luxury Society Members’ data, as well as the Luxury Society websites and the Luxury Society Services.

**Access to and Modification of Your Information**

In compliance with French statute n° 78-17 dated January, 6 1978, you have the rights to access, modify, rectify and suppress any personal information at any time by logging into your account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Settings.

CNIL reference:   
Declaration n° 1344673   
Date: 06.02.2009

**Children**

The Luxury Society website is not intended for children under 18 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

If we decide to materially change our Privacy Policy for Luxury Society and Luxury Society Networking, we will post those changes through a prominent notice on the web site so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it.

This policy became effective December, 2008.
